[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":51317,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":68369,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":19319,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":87692,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2289,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":89984,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4149,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":94135,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1699,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":95837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4439,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":100282,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":967,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":101255,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3309,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":104567,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":877,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":105447,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or  bigger,  you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":109376,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":981,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":110359,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7678,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":118039,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":927,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":118969,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2779,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":121751,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":2664,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":124417,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perfo rm +<sub >6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3612,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":128031,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":814,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":128847,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2166,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":131015,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":839,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":131857,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2596,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":134455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":973,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":135431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":15867,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":151304,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3  is its o wn inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":61,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":151372,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":12336,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":163711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2113,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":165827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element i s the th ing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3739,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":169568,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":865,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":170439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2758,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":173199,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct!  The inve rse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":994,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":174199,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2590,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":176791,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":926,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":177719,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Rememb er, the  inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2926,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":180648,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4168,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":184820,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes","response_history":["yes"],"rt":16555,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":201377,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":47926,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":249306,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because o f this,  we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":41840,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":291151,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":6982,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":298137,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":8098,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":306240,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3341,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":309584,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":5149,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":314735,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5493,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":320232,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1477,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":321711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":" No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5415,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":327128,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":994,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":328124,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":43330,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":371455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":13425,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":384883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3201,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":388087,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 =  10 and  10 - 9 = 1.","rt":784,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":388874,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3193,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":392071,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4230,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":396303,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5806,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":402111,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What  is 5 +<s ub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3453,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":405567,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3597,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":409167,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. Since 4+1 is less than 9, the answer remains the same.","response_history":["5. ","5.","5. Since 4=","5. Since 4+1 is less than 9, the answer remians","5. Since 4+1 is less than 9, the answer remian","5. Since 4+1 is less than 9, the answer remia","5. Since 4+1 is less than 9, the answer  remi","5 . Since 4+1 is less than 9, the answer remains.","5. Since 4+1 is less than 9, the answer remains the same."],"rt":31542,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":440711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 because 8+4=12 which is greater than 9, so you need to subtract 9 from the total. ","response_history":["12","1","3 because 8+4=12 which is grat","3 because 8+4=12 which is gra","3 because 8+4=12 which is greater than 9, so you need to subtracc","3 because 8+4=12 which is greater than 9, so you need to subtract 9 from the total. "],"rt":35435,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":476149,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"fr ee","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract 9 from the sum.","response_history":["0 because ","If the sum is 9 or more then you subr","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract the total","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract the tota","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract the tot","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract the to","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract the t","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract the ","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract the","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract th","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract t","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract 9 from the total.","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract 9 from the total","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract 9 from the tota","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract 9 from the tot","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract 9 from the to","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract 9 f rom the  t","If the sum is 9 or more then you subtract 9 from the sum."],"rt":39064,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":515215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":24103,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":539320,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"0","response_history":["1","0"],"rt":10478,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":549800,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 because  3+3+3=9  which you would then subtract 9 to come to 0.","response_history":["3 becaause","3 becaaus","3 becaau","3 becaa","3 because 3+#+","3 because 3+#","3 because 3+3+#","3 because 3+3+3=9 which you w","3 because 3+3+3=9 which you would then subs","3 because 3+3+3=9 which you would then subtract 9 to come to 0."],"rt":40149,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":589951,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No because 2 is not a multiplier of 9.","response_history":["no","n","No because tw","No because t","No because 2 is not a multiplier of 9."],"rt":16435,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":606388,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes because 3 is a multiplier of 9.","response_history":["Yes because 3 is a multiple","Yes because 3 is a multiplier of 9."],"rt":14152,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":620545,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because 5 is not a multiplier of 9.","response_history":["no because 5 is not a multplier of 9.","no because 5 is not a multiplier of 9."],"rt":12386,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":632936,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because 6 is not a multiplie r of 9.","response_history":["no becas","no because 6 is not a mulplier of 9.","no because 6 is not a multiplier of 9."],"rt":21206,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":654146,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":13522,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":667672,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"0= 1+n","response_history":["1","0= 1 ","0= 1+n"],"rt":32541,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":700215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"0= x+n","response_history":["0= x+n"],"rt":39684,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":739903,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"X must be a multiplier of n so that the result is 0.","response_history":["X must be a mi","X must be a mulp","X must be a multipler of ","X must be a multiplier of n so that the end","X must be a multiplier of n so that the en","X must be a multiplier of n so that the e","X  must be  a multiplier of n so that the result is 0."],"rt":31277,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":771183,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":7870,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":779056,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5629,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":784687,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":6557,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":791247,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"X must be a divisor of n because that would be the only way to have a result of 0.","response_history":["X must be a divisor of n because that would be the only way to have a resuklt","X must be a divisor of n because that would be the only way to have a resukl","X must be a divisor of n because that would be the only way to have a resuk","X must be a divisor of n because that would be the only way to have a resukt","X must be a divisor of n because that would be the only way to hav e a resu k","X must be a divisor of n because that would be the only way to have a result of 0."],"rt":37901,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":829151,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":7356,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":836511,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"It is always correct because x must be a divisor in order to r esult in  0.","response_history":["It is always correct because th","It is always correct because t","It is always correct because x must be a divisor in order to resul ","It is always correct because x must be a divisor in order to result in 0."],"rt":30317,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":866831,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":5694,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":872527,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2703,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":875233,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"28","response_history":["28"],"rt":2476,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":877711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2670,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":880383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Business calculus and statistics. ","response_history":["Business calculus and Bus","Business calculus and Bu","Business calculus and B","Business calculus and ","Business calculus and","Business calculus an","Business calculus and statis","Business calculus and stati","Business calculus and statistics. "],"rt":27270,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":907656,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4414,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":912072,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","response_history":["3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":4789,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":916863,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":5701,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":922567,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you  feel yo u understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"rt":4725,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":927295,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2405,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":929703,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2038,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":931743,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English ","English"],"rt":7118,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":938863,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.","response_history":["No."],"rt":6022,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":944888,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"This was fun!","response_history":["This was fun!"],"rt":5958,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":950847,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.16-0"}]